SANDRA NWAMAKA MEGBULEM

EXECUTIVE ASSISTANT

CONTACT



megbulemsandra@gmail.com



08142738091, 09057094626



C9, Admiralty Homes Estate, Igbon Efon Lekki.



Megbulem Sandra



Amaka Megbulem

CORE SKILLS

.Creative Writing

.Project Management

.Communications (Verbal, Non-Verbal and Interpersonal)

.Fluency in English and French

Intermediate level in Igbo, German, Chinese and Spanish

.Good Team Work and Innovation

.Multitasking and Quick Learning

.Good Grasping Abilities

.Action Oriented and Goal Focused

PROFESSIONAL PROFILE

I am a progressive thinker and avid reader who explores intuition, innovation and feedback when identifying and solving problems. With over seven years cumulated experience of working in the educational, administrative, corporate, service rendering, HR, outsourcing and entertainment sectors, I have built key communication, management, creative writing and analytical skills. I am keen about continuous learning, thoroughness, perfectionism and have a dynamic work ethic.

CAREER OBJECTIVES

I would love to obtain a long term career with a reputable organization as I believe this provides a good opportunity for enhancement of personal and professional status.

WORK EXPERIENCE

Executive Associate

Stanton Chase Lagos/International Group September 2020 - Present

Stanton Chase Lagos is an International Executive Search and Leadership Development Firm and Recruitment Agency, and a part of the Stanton Chase International Group

Key Responsibilities

- Assignment Reporting
- Invoicing/Financial Duties
- Research
- Secretarial Duties

Executive Assistant

Kimberly Ryan Limited | September 2020-Present.

Kimberly Ryan Consult is a Human Resources and Business Solutions provider.

SOFTWARE SKILLS

.General Computer Appreciation (Pack Office, Word, Excel, PowerPoint, Outlook)

.Microsoft Teams

.Photoshop

.Indesign

.Zoom

.Canva

EDUCATION

University of Lagos State, UNILAG.

2019/In-view

M.A French

University of Benin City, UNIBEN.

2013 - 2017

B.A French - Second Class Upper

Centre International de Recherche et d'Etude de Langues (CIREL) – Village du Benin, Lome, Togo.

2016

Certificat du Stage: Translation: French-English, English-French

Command Secondary School Mbiri, Delta State.

2006 - 2012

Key Responsibilities

- Document and Database Management
- Project Management
- Research and Reporting
- Creating invoices (Oil & Gas)
- Acquiring Licenses, Permits and Insurance (NAFDAC, DPR, NIPEX, WAPIC, etc)
- Real Estate Management (rent collection, acquiring property and furnishing)
- Account Maintenance (electronic banking, account opening, transfer instructions, etc)
- Sending and Receiving Correspondence
- Travel Itineraries (booking flights, hotels, transportation and logistics, etc)
- Recruitment and Outsourcing
- Proxy Capacity

Tutor

Ma Petite France NG | July 2019 - Present

Ma Petite France NG is an educational institution founded to suit the demands of Nigeria's teeming desire and interest for French language.

Key Responsibilities

- Tutor kids, teenagers and adults French in a fun way
- Day to day administration
- Interpretation
- Event Planning

Key Achievements

- Successfully raised bilingual children and taught adults another foreign language.
- Successfully planned events that encourage the learning of French language.
- Fostered relations between foreign and national bodies, persons and institutions by serving as an interpreter.

PROFESSIONAL CERTIFICATIONS

International Centre for Language Resources, ICLR

2020

Chinese Language Certificate

Alliance Francais, Enugu/Asaba

2012

DFI F DAI F A2

VOLUNTEERING

.Life and Style Manager, Editorial and Publicity Department, Batch B Stream II 2019 National Youth Service Corps.

Deputy Editor-In-Chief, Orientation Broadcasting Service, Batch B Stream II 2019 Lagos State Orientation Camp.

INTERESTS

.Reading, Writing and Drawing

- .Culinary Escapades
- .Singing and Dancing

Sports (Football, Lawn Tennis and Badminton)

- .Travel and Tourism
- .Modeling, Presenting and Acting
- .Learning
- .Stimulating Conversations

.Art

.Social Media Activism

Presenter

Voice of the Street Television VOSTVNG | September 2018 - July 2019.

Voice of the Street Television is an entertainment channel committed to discovering street styles and talent and bringing them to limelight.

Key Responsibilities

- Present and host a TV show
- Handle Voxpop
- Prepare viewers' playlist
- Organize interviews
- Social media management

Key Achievements

- Successfully handled interactions with clients who sought to promote their music content on our music streaming platform.
- Produced compelling content for television shows, interviews and voxpops.
- Built strong relationships with other media outlets and personalities to ensure seamless interactions and result driven partnerships.
- Induced a remarkable increase in followership of the channel on social media.

Teacher/Personal Assistant to the Proprietor

Skyset International Academy, Asaba | 2013 – 2018

Skyset international academy is a school with international standards that provides crèche, nursery, primary and secondary school services.

Key Responsibilities

- Teach French from Primary 1 SS3
- Manage and distribute information within the office.
- Take memos and maintain files.
- Setup meetings and schedule appointments.
- Take inventory, hotel bookings and travel arrangements.
- Ensure efficient operation at the office.

REFEREES

Tony Onwu

CEO, Kimberly Ryan Limited

Tosin Adesina

Founder, Ma Petite France NG

• Mr. Callistus Ofonye

S.A to the Executive Governor, Enugu State (Electronic Media)/Proprietor, Skyset International Academy, Asaba.

Mrs. Joyce Madaki

Head of Editorial and Publicity
Department, National Youth Service
Corps, Lagos State.

• Miss Ebele Lauren Evi

CEO, Studio Ivhills

(Contact information available upon request)

Key Achievements

- Made impact in kids' lives by teaching them in a fun, unforgettable way.
- Fostered good relationships between parents and the school.
- Impressively assisted the proprietor in administration.

Personal Assistant

Studio Ivhills | 2017 - 2018

Studio Ivhills is a studio which provides beauty and photography services.

Key Responsibilities

- Assist CEO in day to day running of the studio
- Render services to clients
- Create content for social media posts

Key Achievements

- Built a strong clientele.
- Learned how to apply professional makeup.
- Successfully assisted the CEO